pcwallpaperzone.com 2013-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Creativebug

Creativebug, Inc.  
www.creativebug.com  
Website Privacy Policy  
Revised as of November 5, 2012 

## Introduction

Welcome to the www.creativebug.com network of websites and Applications (the “Site”) of Creativebug, Inc., a California corporation (“Creativebug,” also referred to herein as “us,” “we” and “our”). Thank you for your interest in using our services (“Services”) and tangible products (separately, “Products,” and collectively “Offerings”).

We have created this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy’) to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of visitors to our Site and our registered users. Our primary goals in collecting user information are to provide and improve the Site, application, services, features and content, to administer your use of the Site, and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

We are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of personally identifiable information (“PII”) you share with us. PII and the phrases “personally identifiable information” and “personal information” mean any information by which you, individually, can be identified (e.g., your name, address, zip code, telephone number, etc., whether alone or in combination with other information provided by you or that may be available publicly or from other sources.) The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you when you visit our Site how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct, your information.

BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.

## A Special Notice About Children

Children (under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site. In any event, children should not submit any PII to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may not use the Site or any of our Offerings. We abide by the United States Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children younger than age eighteen (18). If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with PII without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@creativebug.com](mailto:support@creativebug.com). If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with PII, we will endeavor to delete such information from our files.

## General

You may visit the home page and certain pages of the Site containing general information without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. When available, we automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, Internet domain address from which you visit the Site (IP address or ISP domain name), and navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used.

## Personally Identifiable Information

### What information is collected

When you register with us or request or receive an Offering, however, the general information described above may be linked to you personally. When you register with us, we will also ask you to provide certain PII, which may include but is not necessarily limited to your name, address, country, company, email address, and a password. We may also collect additional information such as your preferences, and interests. When you purchase an Offering, we will ask for credit card information (name, number, expiration date and access code), and other information necessary to complete the transaction. We may maintain a record of your online purchases, if any. If you post materials on the Site with certain PII (e.g., your name and/or state), we will post the PII that you request we post; and we may link your postings with other PII (e.g., your account with us) for our internal purposes.

Whether or not you choose to provide the information we request is entirely up to you. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to access certain Services, Products offers, and content on the Site.

### How your information is used

We use the foregoing information to establish user accounts; provide the Offerings, including supporting and completing the transactions or other requested activity; communicate with you regarding your subscription or account; provide you with information you have requested, news and updates, and information about Offerings (including future Products and Services that may suit your particular interests); customize and personalize content to you; administer and run the Site, and comply with legal requirements. We also use your personal information to help identify you if you lose your password and to help you quickly find information on the Site. We may use PII to identify patterns and trends of use, but will not release or publish any such information except in a manner that we think in good faith preserves your anonymity.

We may collect financial and/or billing information, such as a payment method and credit card number associated with your personal identity. We may provide this information to a third-party payment clearing house service and use this information to facilitate payment to or by us or as otherwise described above. We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission of the information you submit to us when you use our secure online forms. We store your credit card information remotely in a third-party maintained Level 1 PCI DSS Compliant environment.

However, as with email generally, email that you send us is not necessarily secure against interception. If your email communication includes sensitive information, including but not limited to sensitive PII such as your bank account number, credit or charge card numbers, or Social Security number, you should contact us by mail or telephone. YOU AGREE THAT CREATIVEBUG IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY INTERCEPTED INFORMATION SENT VIA EMAIL, AND HEREBY RELEASE US FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE UNAUTHORIZED INTERCEPTION OR USE OF EMAILED INFORMATION.

## Sharing your information with third parties

We respect the privacy interests of our registered users. Consequently, as of the Revision Date shown above, Creativebug® does not rent, sell or exchange PII to others for marketing purposes without your express, affirmative consent (e.g., by “opting in”). If you do so consent, registered users of the Site who are California residents may request certain information regarding the Company’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

We will share your personal information with our partners and with third-party independent contractors such as unaffiliated service providers, possibly including third parties that reside in jurisdictions with less restrictive data laws than your own jurisdiction, for purposes that include: (i) hosting the Site; (ii) approving and enabling your use of the Site and use or purchase of our Offerings, and performing other functions on our behalf; (iii) providing you with our own service or product offers; and (iv) tracking information generated through the Site. Our partners and third-party independent contractors are obligated contractually not to use or share your personal information for unauthorized purposes. This means we generally restrict access to PII to qualified Creativebug employees and agents with a need to know in order to perform their respective duties. (Our “agents” may include third-party service providers.) However, we share PII only with companies we control that are subject to this Privacy Policy, or with companies whose privacy policies are generally as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy. The Site is designed to transmit a customer’s credit card data via its payment gateway only to the appropriate credit card company and/or credit card payment processing company.

We may also disclose your personal information to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process; to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; to protect and defend Company, its subsidiaries and affiliates (if any), and their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; to enforce the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Site, including without limitation this Privacy Policy; to prevent imminent physical harm; and in the event that we find that your actions on the Site violate any laws, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, this Site uses appropriate industry standard procedures to try to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including firewalls, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. As a result, although we strive to protect your personal information, creativebug.com cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

We may transfer part or all of your information in the case of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or other sale of all or a portion of our assets or stock, provided that the third party agrees to implement a privacy policy similar to this one.

## Reviewing and requesting changes to your information

If you would like to modify your PII on our database, please log onto your account by clicking the “Login” link on the website. Registered Users of the Site may modify their privacy settings, and may correct, modify and update their PII prospectively at any time by logging into their account and making their desired changes. Registered users may also “unregister” or by asking that their registration information be deleted, in which case we will remove them from our list of registered users. Notwithstanding the above, we reserve the right to retain PII in our archival files until we determine there is no potential need for such information, at which point we will use reasonable steps to delete the unregistered user’s PII from our records. We may retain such information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions of use. In addition, it may not be technologically possible or feasible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us. A copy of your personal information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. Removed information may also persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to others.

Where you make use of the social networking and online features of the Site to share information with other individuals on the Site (such as but not limited to submitting comments or questions via feedback, posting photos or other materials on the Site, or submitting an entry to a contest or poll) it may not be possible or practical for us to remove such communications and materials or any associated PII, and such communications, materials, and information may persist, including on third-party computers and other media.

Any questions you may have regarding this Policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of your personal information, or any requests that we correct, update, or remove your information in our databases, should be directed via email to [support@creativebug.com](mailto:support@creativebug.com) or via regular mail to:

255 Kansas St, Suite 302  
San Francisco, CA 94103

## Use of Technology

### IP Address and Cookies

We use your internet protocol address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. We also use your internet protocol address to help identify you.

The Site places “cookies” on your computer’s hard drive through your web browsers to keep track of your identity for the purposes of saving Workshops you bookmark and saving your logged-in state so that you do not have to log in each time you visit the Site. Cookies are small files that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing the Web site. They allow the Site to recognize your computer when you access the Site.

You do have control over your cookies. For more information about working with cookies, you should consult the “help” function of your specific browser and operating system software. Please be advised that if you block or remove cookies from your computer, the Site will not recognize your computer and you may not have access to all portions of the Site.

### Web Beacons

We may use electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel or clear gifs) in HTML emails sent to users to determine whether the emails are opened and thus use valid email addresses. We may also periodically use web beacons to track information about Site pages you visit. The information from the use of these technological methods may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable and may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf.

## Links to Other Websites

The Site contains links to other websites as an accommodation to the respective third-party site owners and for your convenience. Sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under our control, and we shall have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any linked sites, or any link or linking program at any time. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, security practices or the content of such websites. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the website sponsor when linking to other websites.

## Security and Phishing

We implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information, to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. Do not share it with others. Creativebug will never ask you for your password. If you need a new user name and/or password, we may require you to follow certain security procedures (such as providing us with certain PII or correctly answering certain security questions). If satisfied, we will generate a new user name and password automatically through our computers and send it to your email. You may never use another's account without permission. When creating your account, you must provide accurate and complete information. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account. You agree to notify Creativebug immediately of any suspected or known breach of security or unauthorized use of your account. Although Creativebug will not be liable for your losses caused by any unauthorized use of your account, you may be liable for the losses of Creativebug or others due to such unauthorized use.

Identity theft and phishing are of great concern to Creativebug. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your Creativebug account number, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited email or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website at http://www.ftc.gov.

## Testimonials

With your affirmative consent we may post your testimonial on the Site along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at [support@creativebug.com](mailto:support@creativebug.com).

## Affiliate Program

If you participate in our Affiliate Program, we will collect your name, website name, website URL, email address and affiliate program payment preferences (including, but not limited to, bank account number and routing number, bank account name, PayPal account email address, billing address and other financial information). We use this information to enable your participation in the Affiliate Program and to make payments related to it.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Site. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our email notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Site.

## Contacting Creativebug

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or your dealings with this Site, please contact our customer service department using one of the following modes:

Email: [support@creativebug.com](mailto:support@creativebug.com)  
Postal mail: 255 Kansas St, Suite 302, San Francisco, CA 94103 

## Effective Date and Changes

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 5, 2012. We reserve the right to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time and in our sole discretion, as described above. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE AFTER WE CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY WILL CONSTITUTE BINDING ACCEPTANCE OF THOSE CHANGES.
